yamaha-motor-india.com 2017-11-07

# India Yamaha Motor - Revs Your Heart

Thank you for visiting **India Yamaha Motor Pvt. Ltd.** ("Yamaha") website. Yamaha values your right of privacy and wants you to feel comfortable while visiting at www.yamaha-motor-india.com (the "Yamaha Website" or "Website"). This Privacy Policy pertains to the usage of website, disclosures of your personal information etc. Using or visiting Website signify your acceptance and consent to both the contents of this Privacy Policy and the General Terms and Conditions of the Website which are published at www.yamaha-motor-india.com. If you do not agree to any of these terms, it is advised you should not use Website or disclose personal information.

**APPLICABILITY**

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Website, which may contain links to third party websites for your convenience. Yamaha has no control over and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party website, which may collect both passive and personally identifiable information. By using links of third party Websites through Yamaha web site, you expressly relieve Yamaha from any and all liabilities arising from your use of any third party website. We advise you to read carefully privacy policy of third party website before submitting your information.

**WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND USE?**

When you visit Website we may collect passive information about your visit. Passive information is any form of aggregate data, navigational data, tracking data, click-stream data or historical data, which does not on its own personally identify you. Passive Information includes information collected through cookies and web beacons. When you register for the contest or submit other data through Website, we may also obtain and collect personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is information collected online that personally identifies you, such as by name, email address, or mailing address. Yamaha provides you with the ability to "opt-out" of certain uses of such personally identifiable information. However, we do not collect any personally identifiable information without your consent and knowledge.

**MAINTENANCE & OPT-OUT OF INFORMATION**

If you wish to opt-out of our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information, other than as expressly permitted in this Privacy Policy, you will have the option to do so when you first submit your personally identifiable information via the Website. Simply state your desire to opt-out where indicated. If you wish to amend or delete any personally identifiable information that you have previously provided without opt-out, please send us a message at info@yamaha-motor-india.com. We will endeavour to provide a simple way to review, correct, update or remove personally identifiable information you have given us. If you wish to stop receiving a Yamaha newsletter or other circulation, if any, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions contained in each newsletter.

**HOW DO WE USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

If you have opted out our general use of personally identifiable information, Yamaha will not use or disclose such information except as follows 

  * To communicate directly with you in connection with your specific requests
  * To validate entries and winners
  * To permit our website designers to develop features and services that meet your needs
  * To tailor your experience on our Website, showing you individually tailored content
  * To comply with a lawful subpoena or court order
  * To remedy any violation or breach of an agreement between you and Yamaha; and
  * To prevent harm to the property or rights of Yamaha or its customers

If you have not "opted-out" our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information, Yamaha may also use such information for its own marketing and survey purposes and Yamaha may appoint third party agents in connection with such marketing and survey efforts, subject to a confidentiality agreement concerning the information. Yamaha will not, however, disclose any personally identifiable information for use in connection with a third party's marketing efforts.

**AGGREGATE INFORMATION**

Yamaha may share aggregate statistical information with business partners, or other third parties, but none of them receive personally identifiable sponsors information. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of visitors visited a certain area on a website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women applied for extended service, but we would not disclose anything that uniquely identifies those individuals.

**UNSOLICITED EMAILS RECEIVED BY YOU**

Yamaha does not send unsolicited bulk emails to anyone who has requested that we do not contact them. We send newsletters only to those who have taken affirmative steps to subscribe. If you have inadvertently received one of our newsletters, or if you simply wish to stop receiving them, please follow the "Unsubscribe" instructions contained in each newsletter or send a request to be unsubscribed to info@yamaha-motor-india.com

**COOKIES**

Your browser software includes a feature called "cookies." We may use "cookies" to enhance your experience with our site. If enabled, cookies may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the Website, including your page preferences. Cookies tell us nothing about you personally, unless you specifically give us additional information. Yamaha does not merge or associate our cookie information with any personally identifiable information obtained by us or from third parties. Cookies simply assist us in tracking which of our features you like best and what content you may have viewed during past visits. When you re-visit the Website, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: (i) keep count of your return visits to the Website; (ii) accumulate anonymous, aggregate, statistical information on website usage; (iii) deliver content specific to your interests or past viewing history; and (iv) save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites. You can also disable cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you can accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set.

**P3P (PLATEFORM FOR PRIVACY PREFERENCE) CONFORMANCE**

Our cookies conform to the emerging P3P privacy standard, developed by the World Wide Web Consortium. P3P provides a simple, automated way for users to control the use of personal information. . At its most basic level, P3P is a standardized set of multiple-choice questions, covering all the major aspects of a website's privacy policy. Taken together, they present a clear snapshot of how a site handles personal information. P3P-enabled browsers can "read" this snapshot automatically and compare it to the consumer's own set of privacy preferences. P3P places privacy policies where users can find them, in a form users can understand, and, most importantly, enables users to act on what they see.

**IP ADDRESSES**

An Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a number assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. An Internet Service Provider ("ISP") typically assigns a random dynamic IP address at the time of your dial-up. For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, a static IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. Yamaha may record the IP addresses of visitors to its Website. While an IP address may reveal your ISP or geographic area, we cannot determine your identity solely based upon your IP address. Other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages, but these IP addresses are never associated with Internet users.

**WEB BEACONS**

The Website may contain web beacons, which are electronic images (sometimes called "single-pixel gifs") that allow us to count page views, or to access cookies. We may also include web beacons in HTML-formatted newsletters containing graphics that we may send to opt-in subscribers, to count the number of newsletters that have been opened and read. Our web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor, or share any personal information about our website visitors. They are used only to compile our anonymous, aggregate statistics about website usage.

**COMPUTER PROFILES**

Yamaha may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data that helps us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For example, we may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. None of this information is personally identifiable and we only share this information in the aggregate, reflecting overall website or Internet usage trends, as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**CHAT ROOMS AND FORUMS**

The Website may in the future include chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. If so, Yamaha as a passive conduit will not be liable for any of the transmitted information. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution before disclosing your personal information via these public venues, which you do at your own risk. If you do so, you may receive unsolicited emails or "spam." Yamaha cannot safeguard the privacy of personally identifiable information that is disclosed and can be viewed or accessed online in this manner.

**SECURITY**

Some pages of the Website use security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information that is transmitted through the Website. When you use a secure browser, all information you submit comes to us. We maintain our servers in locked facilities with secure access. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. You can report network abuse and any risk of security violations to us.

**CHILDRE'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION**

Yamaha does not knowingly collect contact or personally identifiable information from children under 18. The Website is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 18, and is designed to block our knowing acceptance of any such information, wherever age related information is requested. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under 18. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under 18, please do so by emailing us at info@yamaha-motor-india.com

**AMENDMENTS**

Yamaha reserve its discretion to amend any of the condition of this policy without any prior intimation.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@yamaha-motor-india.com, or at the following address: Back Office, India Yamaha Motor Pvt. Ltd., A-3, Surajpur Industrial Area, Noida- Dadri Road, Greater Noida, Gautam Budh Nagar, Uttar Pradesh -201306.
